bloggerstop.net 2011-09-02

# BloggerStop.Net | Privacy Policy

## BloggerStop.Net - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**Collection of Personal Information**   
When visiting [BloggerStop](http://bloggerstop.net/), the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the date and time of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Links to third party Websites**   
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own. 

**Third Party ad servers**   
Third Party ad servers, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. These cookies enable them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet. BloggerStop has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers. 

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**   
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. 

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of [BloggerStop.Net](http://bloggerstop.net/) then you may contact us at admin@mail.bloggerstop.net 

This privacy policy was generated by the [Easy Privacy Policy](http://europeancruiseadvisor.com/) plugin for WordPress.
